Guide to the Jewish Community Council of Greater Washington records, 1937-1988 MS2012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1937-1988; MS2012 Series 4; 11 Linear feet
  - JCCGW - Early History of the Council by Mrs. Henry Gichner, Circa 1950 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - JCCGW - Founding of the Council 1938-1948 by Hasia Diner, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - JCCGW Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - JCCGW Self Study, 1951 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - JCCGW Self Study, 1951 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - JCCGW 20th Anniversary, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - JCCGW 20th Anniversary, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - JCCGW 30th Anniversary, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Community Organization in the U.S., 1943-1949 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Defense League (JDL), 1969 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - JDL, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - JDL, 1971 January (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - JDL, 1971 February-May (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - JDL, 1971 June-December (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - JDL, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - JDL, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Jewish Education - "Enrollment and School Patterns of Jewish Schools in Greater Washington,", 1961-1962 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Jewish Education - Jewish Day Schools of Greater Washington DC, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Jewish Education - Jewish Day Schools of Greater Washington DC, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Jewish Hospital - "The Facts About A Jewish Hospital for Washington" Survey, 1948 June (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Jewish Memorial Hospital Association (JMHA), 1966-1968 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - JMHA, 1969 January-September (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - JMHA, 1969 October-December (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - JMHA, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Occupational Distribution, 1947 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Population - Canada, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Population - "National Jewish Population Survey" Minutes, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Population - "National Jewish Population Survey" Background Materials, 1956-1964 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Population - "National Jewish Population Survey" Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Population - "National Jewish Population Survey" Minutes, Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Population - "National Jewish Population Survey" Pre-Prospectus; Proposal, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Population - "National Jewish Population Survey" Prospectus, Working Memos no. 1-2, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Population - "National Jewish Population Survey" Working Memo no. 3, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Population - "National Jewish Population Survey" Working Memos no. 4-5, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Population - "National Jewish Population Survey" Questionnaire, sections A-D, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Population - "National Jewish Population Survey" Questionnaire, sections E-F, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Jewish Population - "National Jewish Population Survey" Questionnaire, sections G-I (end), 1963 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Jewish Population - Washington DC Jewish Population Survey, 1948-1950 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Jewish Population - Washington DC Jewish Population Survey, Correspondence, 1956-1959 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Jewish Population - Washington DC Jewish Population Survey, Correspondence, Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Jewish Population - Washington DC Jewish Population Survey Report, 1957 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Population - Washington DC Jewish Population Survey Reviews, 1958-1960 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Prisoners - Rights of Jewish Prisoners at Lorton Reformatory, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Jews for Urban Justice, 1967 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Jews for Urban Justice - A Report on Social Action and the Jewish Community, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Jews for Urban Justice, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Jews for Urban Justice, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Jews for Urban Justice, 1970 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Jews for Urban Justice - Study by Harold Goldberg, 1970 March (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Jews for Urban Justice - Correspondence re Goldberg Study of JUJ, 1970 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Jews for Urban Justice, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Kay, Abraham S. (member JCCGW executive council), 1950-1965 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Kennedy - Jewish Community Tribute to JFK, 1963 November 25 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Kennedy - Candlelight Memorial, 1963 December 22 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Kennedy - Candlelight Memorial Clippings, 1963 December 22 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - King, Martin Luther, 1963-1977 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Ku Klux Klan, 1949-1961 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Ku Klux Klan Law Suit, 1977-1978 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Ku Klux Klan Law Suit, 1977-1978 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Latin America - Jews in Argentina, 1966 July (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Lyon, Richard K. - President of JCCGW, 1964-1967 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - McCarthyism, 1953-1964 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Metz, Rabbi Solomon H. - First President of JCCGW (eulogies), 1959 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Middle East Institute Conference, 1959 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Muslims - Continuing Committee on Muslim-Christian Cooperation, 1958 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Muslims - Institute on Muslim-Christian Cooperation, 1959 February 26-27 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Muslims - Institute on Muslim-Christian Cooperation: Exchange between I. Franck and Garland Hopkins, 1959 February-March (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Muslims - Institute on Muslim-Christian Cooperation: Reactions to Hopkins-Franck Exchange, 1959-1964 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Namibia, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1949-1971 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials (NAIRO), 1952-1959 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - NAIRO, 1960-1965 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews (NCCJ), 1949-1951 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - NCCJ, 1952-1956 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - NCCJ, 1957-1962 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - NCCJ, 1963-1964 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - NCCJ, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - NCCJ, 1977-1982 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - NCCJ - "The Dialogue,", 1963 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - NCCJ - "The Dialogue,", 1964-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews Survey (NCCJ), 1979 February (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - NCCJ - Metropolitan Washington Human Relations Executives, 1978-1979 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - National Council of Churches Middle East Task Force, 1980 January-April (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - National Council of Churches Middle East Task Force, 1980 May-November (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - National Conference of Jewish Communal Service (NCJCS), 1953-1966 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - NCJCS, 1975-1977 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - NCJCS - Survey of Women Professionals in Jewish Communal Service, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - National Conference of Jewish Communal Service, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - National Conference of Jewish Communal Service, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - New Jewish Agenda, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Nuclear Weapons Freeze, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - People's Organization of Montgomery County (POMCO), 1968-1969 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Rabbinical Assembly of America - Commission of Social Action, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Race Labeling in Newspaper Articles, 1950-1955 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Race Relations Subcommittee, 1960-1962 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Reapportionment of State Legislatures - American Jewish Congress Statement, 1965 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Restrictive Covenants, 1940 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Restrictive Covenants, 1946 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Restrictive Covenants, 1947-1949 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Restrictive Covenants, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Restrictive Covenants, 1951-1952 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Restrictive Covenants, 1953-1962 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Rodman, Morris (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Sesquicentennial Observance - Washington DC 150th Anniversary, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Gerald L.K., 1944-1946 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Gerald L.K., 1947 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Gerald L.K., 1948-1952 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Gerald L.K., 1953-1955 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Tercentenary, American Jewish, 1954 September-October (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Tercentenary, American Jewish, 1954 November-December (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Tercentenary, American Jewish, 1955-1956 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Turover, Isador, 1951-1967 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - United Synagogue of America - "Judaism in Social Action,", 1973 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Vietnam War - JCCGW Debates re Adopting a Position on Vietnam War, 1969 October (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Vietnam War - Vietnam Moratorium, 1969 October-November (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Vietnam War - Sim Shalom: Ad Hoc Peace Committee of the Greater Washington Jewish Community, 1969-1970 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Vietnam War - Festival of Life and Reconstruction in Vietnam, 1973 January 13-17 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Voice of America, 1951-1952 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Washington, D.C. Board of Jewish Education, 1964-1965 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Washington, D.C. Board of Jewish Education - Annual Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Washington Board of Rabbis, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Washington Board of Rabbis, 1976 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Washington Board of Rabbis, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Washington Board of Rabbis, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Washington Board of Rabbis, 1979-1980 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Washington, D.C. Community Renewal, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Washington, D.C. Council of Social Agencies - "The Social Survey: Race Relations,", 1946 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Washington, D.C. Council of Social Agencies - "The Social Survey: Religious Relations,", 1946 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Washington, D.C. Riots, 1968 March (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Washington, D.C. Riots 1968 - JCCGW Response to King Assassination and Riots, 1968 April (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Washington, D.C. Riots 1968 - Washington City Council Hearings on Rebuilding and Recovery, 1968 April (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Washington, D.C. Riots 1968 - Meetings of Washington Community Organizations, 1968 April (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Washington, D.C. - Washington Civil Disorder Survey, 1968 May (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Washington, D.C. Riots 1968 - JCCGW Survey of Jewish Businessmen Suffering Losses During Washington Riots, 1968 April (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Washington, D.C. Schools - Study by Harry Passow, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Wolf, Seymour David - JCCGW President, 1967-1972 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Wolfsohn, Joel D. - JCCGW President, 1961-1962 (Box 92, Folder 19)
- Oversized material, 1949-1981; MS2012 Series 5; 1 Linear feet (Oversize-folder UP0045, Box 93)
  This series consists of materials that were too large to fit in their companion boxes. The nine items include: a 1947 reprint from The New Leader, on how to deal with the anti-Semitic Gerald L.K. Smith; a 1949 poster of newspaper clippings related to religion in public schools; a 1952 Courier (a publication of the United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization); a 1955 reprint from Look magazine on the position of Jews in America; a newspaper insert, "The Jericho March," related to Soviet Jewry in the 1960's; a handbill for a rally on behalf of Soviet Jews in 1971; a 1974 fund raising poster from ProJeCt, a Washington interreligious alliance; a newspaper board game from 1975 concerning emigration of Soviet Jews; and a 1981 poster from an audio-visual presentation on Jerusalem.
  - Religious Holiday Observance in the Public Schools (originally from Box 21, folder 1), 1949 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry - Community Action Programs (originally from Box 31, folder 3), 1965-1970 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Identity Week for Soviet Jewry (originally from Box 33, folder 14), 1971 June 23-27 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Jerusalem Exhibit - Montgomery Mall (originally from Box 55, folder 22), 1981 June 01-14 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry Seminar (originally from Box 58, folder 15), 1975 November 09 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - ProJeCt (originally from Box 69, folder 17), 1974 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Anti-Semitism - General (originally from Box 73, folder 3), 1952-1959 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Human Rights of Minorities - UN Charter (originally from Box 83, folder 25), 1945-1952 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Gerald L.K. (originally from Box 91, folder 7), 1947 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- 2007 Accession, 1987-2004; MS2012 Series 6; 18 Linear feet
  This series contains documents and photographs that was donated in 2007. This is a container list of the box content. The series is not fully processed.
  - Religion in School, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 1)
  - Tours, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 2)
  - Medicare Return, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 3)
  - Montgomery Foundation Grant, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Labor Commit, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 5)
  - JSSA Financial, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 6)
  - Speaking Engagements, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Reception, 2000 (Box UP07-1, Folder 8)
  - Legis Task Force, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 9)
  - State Boards and Commissions, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 10)
  - Governor Reception, 2000 (Box UP07-1, Folder 11)
  - MD Legislative Reception, 2002 (Box UP07-1, Folder 12)
  - 98 Legislative Task Force, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 13)
  - Legis Task Force, 2001 (Box UP07-1, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Alerts, 1999 (Box UP07-1, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Correspondence, 1999 (Box UP07-1, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Compilations, 1999 (Box UP07-1, Folder 17)
  - Mental Health, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Wrap Up, 1999 (Box UP07-1, Folder 19)
  - Legislative Reception, 1998 (Box UP07-1, Folder 20)
  - MJA Issues, 1999 (Box UP07-1, Folder 21)
  - Legislative Reception, 2001 (Box UP07-1, Folder 22)
  - MD Legislative Reception, 1998 (Box UP07-1, Folder 23)
  - MD Alliance for the Poor, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 24)
  - MILC, 1999 (Box UP07-1, Folder 25)
  - Mid East Forum DCJCC, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 26)
  - MoCo Supplement, 1999 (Box UP07-1, Folder 27)
  - Earned Income Tax Credit, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 28)
  - Food Stamps, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 29)
  - Senior Issues, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 30)
  - Legis Task Force, 2001 (Box UP07-1, Folder 31)
  - Newsletter, 2001 (Box UP07-1, Folder 32)
  - NOVA, 1999 (Box UP07-1, Folder 33)
  - Non-profit Alliance, 2000 (Box UP07-1, Folder 34)
  - Newsletter, 1998 (Box UP07-1, Folder 35)
  - MD News Articles, 1998 (Box UP07-1, Folder 36)
  - NCSJ, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 37)
  - Washington Leadership Summit, 1999 (Box UP07-1, Folder 38)
  - Patients Bill of Rights - Federal, 1999 (Box UP07-1, Folder 39)
  - RAPID, 1999 (Box UP07-1, Folder 40)
  - Charles Ramsey, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 41)
  - DC Mayor Anthony Williams, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 42)
  - CDBG Applications, undated (Box UP07-1, Folder 43)
  - Jewish News in Review - Maxell 66/33, undated (Box UP07-2, Folder 1)
  - Jewish News in Review - FUJIFILM 33, undated (Box UP07-2, Folder 2)
  - Jewish News in Review - Maxell 126/63, undated (Box UP07-2, Folder 3)
  - Jewish News in Review - VHS, undated (Box UP07-2, Folder 4)
  - Jewish News in Review - Montgomery Video Productions, undated (Box UP07-2, Folder 5)
  - VHS - various, undated (Box UP07-2, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Community Hour, undated (Box UP07-2, Folder 7)
  - Jewish News in Review, undated (Box UP07-3, Folder 1)
  - Those Who Wait, undated (Box UP07-3, Folder 2)
  - Building a Washington Community - Jewish Community Hour, undated (Box UP07-3, Folder 3)
  - Glimpses of Abba Eban's Heritage - Jewish Community Hour, undated (Box UP07-3, Folder 4)
  - "Through Our Survivors' Eyes", undated (Box UP07-3, Folder 5)
  - African American/Jewish Seder, undated (Box UP07-3, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Community Council - 1998 Israel Study Tour, undated (Box UP07-3, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Community Relations - Jewish Community Hour, undated (Box UP07-3, Folder 8)
  - Unlabeled Tape, undated (Box UP07-3, Folder 9)
  - Jewish News in Review - various VHS, undated (Box UP07-3, Folder 10)
  - Grants, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 1)
  - MD State Security Funding, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 2)
  - MoCo 2004 Budget, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 3)
  - Empowerment DHCD FY05, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 4)
  - Federal Grant Info, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 5)
  - MoCo Testimony Book, 2004 (Box UP07-4, Folder 6)
  - MoCo Budget Hearing FY05, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 7)
  - State Bond Bill, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 8)
  - Tax Rebate, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 9)
  - MoCo Budget Advocacy, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 10)
  - Packet of emails for Legislative Reception in Annapolis, 2004 February 09 (Box UP07-4, Folder 11)
  - Packet of emails for MoCo Advocacy Day, 2004 November 14 (Box UP07-4, Folder 12)
  - Packet of emails about "Passion of the Christ", undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 13)
  - CDBG FY05, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 14)
  - Bond Bill FY05, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 15)
  - MoCo Funding FY05, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 16)
  - MoCo Jewish Human Service Requests FY05, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 17)
  - MoCo Jewish Human Service Agency Funding Requests FY99, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 18)
  - MoCo Jewish Human Service Agency Funding Requests FY00, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 19)
  - MoCo Jewish Human Service Agency Funding Requests FY01, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 20)
  - MoCo Jewish Human Service Agency Funding Requests FY02, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 21)
  - Maryland FY04 Budget, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 22)
  - Testimony provided on behalf of the Maryland Association of Area Agencies on Aging, 2003 November 13 (Box UP07-4, Folder 23)
  - MJA - Legislative Report - 1994 session, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 24)
  - MJA - Legislative Report - 1995 session, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 25)
  - MJA - Legislative Report - 1997 session, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 26)
  - DHHS Comm. Serv. FY05, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 27)
  - Programs, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 28)
  - Federation, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 29)
  - Installation 2004 proclamations, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 30)
  - MoCo Advocacy Day, 2004 (Box UP07-4, Folder 31)
  - Super Sunday, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 32)
  - Turkey Bombing Memorial, 2003 November 20 (Box UP07-4, Folder 33)
  - Annual Meeting, 2003 November (Box UP07-4, Folder 34)
  - B'nai Tzedek, 2003 November (Box UP07-4, Folder 35)
  - Saudi Arabian Rally, 2003 September 24 (Box UP07-4, Folder 36)
  - Meetings, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 37)
  - Receptions, undated (Box UP07-4, Folder 38)
  - Hebrew Home Public Relations, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 1)
  - HHS Analysis, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 2)
  - Living and Recovering at the Hebrew Home, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 3)
  - Hebrew Home MC, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 4)
  - Holocaust Restitution, 1999 (Box UP07-5, Folder 5)
  - Home Healthcare, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 6)
  - Holocaust Restitution - Federal, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 7)
  - Iran, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 8)
  - Internet, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 9)
  - Israel - Electoral System, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 10)
  - Israel - Mission, 1997 (Box UP07-5, Folder 11)
  - Israel - Mission, 1999 (Box UP07-5, Folder 12)
  - Israel - Turkey, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 13)
  - JCA - Advocacy Cmte, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 14)
  - 1999 JCA - Older Worker Expo, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 15)
  - JCPA Insider/Press Release, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 16)
  - JCPA Plenum, 1999 (Box UP07-5, Folder 17)
  - JCPA: Bd. and Task Force, 2000 September (Box UP07-5, Folder 18)
  - JCPA Plenum, 2001 (Box UP07-5, Folder 19)
  - JFGH - General, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 20)
  - JFGH - $225,000, 1997 (Box UP07-5, Folder 21)
  - Community Empowerment Grants, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 22)
  - Lt. Gov. Mtg, undated (Box UP07-5, Folder 23)
  - Legis Task Force, 2001 (Box UP07-5, Folder 24)
  - MoCo Legis Recept, 2000 (Box UP07-5, Folder 25)
  - MJA Advocacy Day, 2001 (Box UP07-5, Folder 26)
  - MD Duncan Mtg, 2001 (Box UP07-5, Folder 27)
  - Immigration, 2001 (Box UP07-5, Folder 28)
  - Genetic Discrimination, 2001 (Box UP07-5, Folder 29)
  - UJC Leadership Summit, 2001 (Box UP07-6, Folder 1)
  - Agency Booklet, 2002 (Box UP07-6, Folder 2)
  - Acceptance/Rejection Letters, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 3)
  - County Council Prelim Discussions, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 4)
  - Major Funding Items, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 5)
  - HHS Meetings, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 6)
  - Testimony - MoCo FY02, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, 1999 (Box UP07-6, Folder 8)
  - Advocacy Day, 1998 (Box UP07-6, Folder 9)
  - Action Alert - Income Tax Subtraction, 1998 April (Box UP07-6, Folder 10)
  - Agency Funding Synopsis JFGH, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1998 (Box UP07-6, Folder 12)
  - Agency Profiles, 1998 (Box UP07-6, Folder 13)
  - Agency Profiles, 1999 (Box UP07-6, Folder 14)
  - Del Ali, 1998 October 29 (Box UP07-6, Folder 15)
  - American Jewish Committee, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 16)
  - Ambassador's Address, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 17)
  - Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box UP07-6, Folder 18)
  - Argentinean Jewry, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 19)
  - Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box UP07-6, Folder 20)
  - Baker, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 21)
  - Ballot Questions Testimony, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 22)
  - Bios, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 23)
  - Baltimore - Government Relation, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 24)
  - Board Orientation Meeting, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 25)
  - Board and Commissions, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 26)
  - Baram, Amatzia, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 27)
  - Board Minutes, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 28)
  - Bond Bill, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 29)
  - Harold Brazil, 1998 May 04 (Box UP07-6, Folder 30)
  - Broder, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 31)
  - Campaign Literature, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 32)
  - Kevin Chavous, 1998 February 26 (Box UP07-6, Folder 33)
  - Christian Coalition, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 34)
  - Community Initiative Grant (CIG), undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 35)
  - CHIP, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 36)
  - Computer Notes, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 37)
  - Conference Calls, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 38)
  - Congratulations Letter, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 39)
  - DC Advisory Board, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 40)
  - DC Jarvis Debate, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 41)
  - DC Legislative, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 42)
  - DC Reception, 1998 June 17 (Box UP07-6, Folder 43)
  - Duncan Meeting, 1998 (Box UP07-6, Folder 44)
  - Jack Evans, 1998 January 13 (Box UP07-6, Folder 45)
  - DC - Emergency Preparedness Exercise, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 46)
  - Federal Budget Analysis, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 47)
  - Federation Grants, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 48)
  - Fenty, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 49)
  - Food Stamps, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 50)
  - Genetics, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 51)
  - Genetics, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 52)
  - Issues - Affirmative Action, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 53)
  - Action Alert - Food Stamp Restoration, 1998 April (Box UP07-6, Folder 54)
  - GA, 1999 (Box UP07-6, Folder 55)
  - Glendening Meeting, 1999 (Box UP07-6, Folder 56)
  - Glendening Meeting, 1998 (Box UP07-6, Folder 57)
  - Montgomery County Budget Process, undated (Box UP07-6, Folder 58)
  - Glendening Meeting, 1997 (Box UP07-6, Folder 59)
  - Charitable Choice, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 1)
  - Faith Based Initiative - Charitable Choice - Post Bush, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 2)
  - Washington 14, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 3)
  - The Washington 13 Conference, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 4)
  - Saudi Arabian Rally, 2003 September (Box UP07-7, Folder 5)
  - Karen Spalter's 2002 GA folder, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 6)
  - JCPA - Hill visits, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 7)